const questions = [
    {numb: 1,
      question: "What is the purpose of 'printf' function in C?",
      options: ["a) It reads input from the user", "b) It displays output to the console", "c) It performs arithmetic operations", "d) It declares variables"],
      answer: "b) It displays output to the console"
    },
    {numb: 2,
      question: "What is the correct way to define a constant in C?",
      options: ["a) const int x = 10;", "b) const x = 10;", "c) #define x 10", "d) define constant x = 10;"],
      answer: "a) const int x = 10;"
    },
    {numb: 3,
      question: "What is the syntax to declare an integer variable in C?",
      options: ["a) int x;", "b) x = 5;", "c) integer x;", "d) var x;"],
      answer: "a) int x;"
    },
    {numb: 4,
      question: "Which function is used to take input from the user in C?",
      options: ["a) input()", "b) read()", "c) scanf()", "d) gets()"],
      answer: "c) scanf()"
    },
    {numb: 5,
      question: "What is the result of 5 % 2 in C?",
      options: ["a) 2", "b) 2.5", "c) 1", "d) 0"],
      answer: "c) 1"
    },
    {numb: 6,
      question: "Which data type is used to store floating-point numbers in C?",
      options: ["a) float", "b) char", "c) int", "d) double"],
      answer: "d) double"
    },
    {numb: 7,
      question: "What is the 'sizeof' operator used for in C?",
      options: ["a) To find the size of a variable", "b) To convert data types", "c) To print output", "d) To declare functions"],
      answer: "a) To find the size of a variable"
    },
    {numb: 8,
      question: "What is the output of the following code: \n int x = 10; \n printf(\"%d\", x++); \n printf(\"%d\", x);",
      options: ["a) 1011", "b) 1012", "c) 1111", "d) 1110"],
      answer: "b) 1012"
    },
    {numb: 9,
      question: "What does the 'break' statement do in C?",
      options: ["a) Exits the loop", "b) Continues to the next iteration of the loop", "c) Returns a value from a function", "d) Prints output to the console"],
      answer: "a) Exits the loop"
    },
    {numb: 10,
      question: "What is the purpose of 'malloc' function in C?",
      options: ["a) To free memory", "b) To allocate memory", "c) To print memory addresses", "d) To compare memory contents"],
      answer: "b) To allocate memory"
    }
  ];
  
  